https://www.equip2golf.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Equip2Golf, Inc. respects your privacy. Below is our statement regarding use of information gathered at this site:
Whenever you access a page, your IP address, browser and version, operating system and the site you came from are stored in a log file. This information cannot be used to identify a specific individual. This information is only used for statistical purposes to help improve this site and provide accurate statistics to prospective advertisers in the form of aggregated data.
The email addresses collected from subscription for our email newsletter are not sold or disclosed to third party organizations or individuals. The email addresses collected will only be used to send out the email newsletter. You will not receive any mailings you did not request. You can remove yourself from our list at any time by sending a blank email with “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line to: gary@equip2golf.com from the email address that you subscribed under.
This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies of other such sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each site that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.
If there are questions regarding our privacy statement or if assistance is required in opting out of our email newsletter subscription list please contact gary@equip2golf.com.
@equip2golf
Quick Links
About
Contact
Privacy Policy
Review Policy
Terms of Use
Tags
© 2021 EQUIP2GOLF, INC.
ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
